Guide to the Jack Underhill papers, 1963-1997
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 5: Housing and Urban Development, 1970-1998; (9.5 boxes)
  - General Accounting Office (GAO), 1989-1996 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Homelessness Legislation, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Homelessness Legislation, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Homelessness Legislation, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Homelessness Legislation, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Homelessness Legislation, 1992-1996 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Housing and Urban Development Announcements, 1990s (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Housing and Urban Development: 94 Rule; Forms, 1993-1996 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Housing and Urban Development: Legislative History, 1980-1995 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Legislation, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Legislation, 1990s (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Housing and Urban Development: Memos and Press, 1997 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Office of Program Analysis and Evaluation (OPAE): Community Planning and Development; Atlanta, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Office of Program Analysis and Evaluation (OPAE): Director's Conference; Evaluative Assessment, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Office of Program Analysis and Evaluation (OPAE): Executive Summary; Risk Analysis, 1984-1988 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Reform, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Reform Planning and Operations, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Reports and Staff, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Summary of Articles and Books: Bell Curve - Haar, Charles M., 1990s (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Summary of Articles and Books: Homelessness - Toffler, Alvin, 1990s (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Urban Development Action Grants, 1980-1983 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Urban Development Action Grants, 1980-1983 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - US and USSR: Agreement, Assessment, and Protocol, 1974-1978 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - US and USSR: Housing and Construction in Climate Conditions, 1988-1991 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - US and USSR: Housing and Construction Protocol, 1978-1985 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - US and USSR: Housing and Other Construction Working Group, 1986-1987 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Welfare Reform Analysis, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Welfare Reform Assessment, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Welfare Reform: Summary of Press Comments, 1993-1994 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Welfare Reform: Summary and Analysis, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Welfare Reform: Welfare Reform Literature, 1994 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Series 6: Histories, 1964-1983; (2.5 boxes)
  This series documents the history of a variety of planned communities that the Underhill papers involve. The series has 23 folders in 3 boxes.
  - History of New Communities, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    96.2
  - Reston: A Study in Beginnings Vol. I (Manuscript incomplete) Chapters I-IV, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    82.13
  - Reston: A Study in Beginnings Vol. I (Manuscript incomplete) Chapters VI-XI, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    82.14
  - Historical Material-New Communities, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    140.7
  - Historical Material-New Communities, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    140.10
  - Historical Material-New Communities, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    140.6
  - Historical Material-New Communities, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    140.9
  - Legislative History, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    95.5
  - History I 2a, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    82.15
  - Historical Material-New Communities, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    140.5
  - Legislative History, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    95.6
  - Legal History, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    484.20
    - Memo: Arthur A. Davis and Frederick A. McLaughlin, Jr. to Samuel C. Jackson, "The Goals of the New Communities Program", March 17, 1969; 1.
    - Note: John A. Bell to Mr. Haar, January 7, 1969; 2.
    - Report: Anonymous, "Rules and Regulations: Specifications - Title IV New Communities Program", no date; 3.
  - Legislative History, 1970s (Box 40, Folder 1)
    483.2
    - Memo: William White to the Secretary of the Department of Housing and Urban Development, "New Town-In-Town Executive Summary", February 28, 1978; 1.
    - Paper: Anonymous, "6. Examples of TACLE Program", no date; 2.
    - Paper: Anonymous, "Proposal for Strengthening the Role of New Communities in Implementing National Urban Growth Strategy", no date; 3.
    - Paper: Anonymous, "Recommendations Concerning Innovation in New Communities", no date; 4.
    - Report: New Community Development Corporation, "Appendix I", no date; 5.
    - Report: New Community Development Corporation, "Appendix II, Draft", no date; 6.
    - Report: New Community Development Corporation, "New Program Initiative: New-Town-In-Town", February 6, 1978; 7.
    - Paper: Office of Policy Development and Research Special Studies, "New Communities Policy Options Paper", June 20, 1975; 8.
  - New Communities Administration Administration History, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    130.4
  - New Communities Administration Administration History, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    130.1
  - Historical Material-New Communities, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    140.4
  - New Communities Administration Administration History, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    130.3
  - Project History, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    95.3
  - New Communities Administration Administration History, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    130.2
  - History of New Communities, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    96.1
    - History of New Communities Program, January 18, 1978; 1.
    - History of New Communities, Diagram from "Strategy for New Community Development in the United States.", 1975; 11.
  - Historical Material-New Communities, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    140.8
  - History-Memos, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    80.16
  - History-Memos, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    80.17
  - Historic Tables, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    92.2
  - Budget Administration History, 1980s (Box 41, Folder 5)
    81.2
- Series 7: Finance, 1969-1983; (3.5 boxes)
  The papers in this series all relate to finances. The documents include the budget, different costs, and other information. The series has 32 folders in 4 boxes.
  - Park Forest South Investments, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    97.4
  - New Communities Financing, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    117.3
  - Jonathan Development Corporation 4th Supplemental Indenture of Mortgage, 1970-1972 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    117.5
  - Domestic Growth Policy, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    484.10
    - Proposal: Anonymous, "Proposal for Combining New Community Obligations", no date; 1.
  - National Growth and Development Bank, 1971 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    115.1
  - National Growth and Development Bank, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    115.2
  - Real Estate Financial Reporting-The Urban Land Institute, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    106.2
  - Budget Text Material, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    139.1
  - Cedar Riverside Accounting and Financial Reporting Problems, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    113.2
  - Potential Legislative Proposals, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    482.1
  - Legislation-Federal Financing Bank, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    80.10
  - A Social Audit of Mixed-Income Housing, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    112.3
  - Jonathan New Community Financial Evaluation, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    117.4
  - Jonathan New Community Financial Evaluation, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    109.11
  - Market Factors, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    484.6
  - Newfields: Market and Financial Evaluation, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    97.6
  - Finance II, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    140.1
  - Equity, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    80.18
  - Land Costs, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    81.8
  - Cedar Riverside Properties-Financial Statements, 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    109.5
  - Cedar Riverside Land Company Financial Statements, 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    109.7
  - Stage I Land Company Financial Report (Cedar Riverside), 1977 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    112.7
  - Budget: Legislation-New Initiatives, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    482.10
  - Budget Issue: Legislation-New Initiatives, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    482.9
  - Financial Plan, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    482.7
  - New Communities Administration Appropriation Hearings on FY 1978 Budget (John Clinton's) (Box 43, Folder 10)
    123.1
  - National Development Bank, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    115.3
  - Budget Tax Material, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    139.2
  - Draft-"Reasons for financial problems or success", 1980 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    88.9
  - Budget Tables, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    81.5
  - Finance II, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    139.18
  - Secretary Department of Housing and Urban Development 1983 Budget Proposal Report to Congress, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    103.7
  - Finance, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    141.1
  - Budget Tables, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    81.4
  - Total Costs, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    82.4
  - Housing Costs, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    83.4
  - Draft-Secretary Department of Housing and Urban Development 1984 Budget Proposals Report to Congress, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    103.1
  - NIC Data (Income Tables), 1983 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    97.1
  - Financial Redirection Study, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    482.6
- Series 8: General Information, 1963-1987; (9 boxes)
  This series has information that comes from a variety of topics from the Underhill papers. Topics include reference material, outlines, fact sheets, and other information from different sources. The series has 99 folders in 10 boxes.
  - New Towns Material, 1963-1967 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    110.3
  - New Material, 1963-1967 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    110.4
  - Elk Grove Village-Summary Fact Sheets and Interviews, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    89.6
  - Greenbelt Towns Revisited-booklet, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    139.15
  - New Communities Material, 1967-1969 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    110.1
    - The Mortgage Banker, "New Financing...for Planned Communities", September 1968; 1.
  - New Communities Material, 1967-1969 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    110.2
  - PHS Research Grant-New Towns Research Seminar, 1969-1970 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    107.1
  - PHS Research Grant-New Towns Research Seminar, 1969-1970 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    107.2
  - PHS Research Grant-New Towns Research Seminar, 1969-1970 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    107.3
  - New Towns: Policy Problems in Regulatory Development, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    105.10
  - Blank Forms, 1970s (Box 46, Folder 6)
    139.4
  - Low Income, 1970s (Box 46, Folder 7)
    139.3
  - Blank Forms, 1970s (Box 46, Folder 8)
    138.8
  - New Communities-Staff Paper, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    111.4
  - New Communities-Staff Paper, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    111.5
  - Maumelle Promotional Brochure, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    117.7
  - Photos, 1970s (Box 47, Folder 1)
    484.12
  - Photos, 1970s (Box 47, Folder 2)
    484.11
    - Photograph: Department of Housing and Urban Development, "Annapolis, Maryland", no date; 1.
    - Photograph: Department of Housing and Urban Development, "Cedar Riverside", no date; 2.
    - Photograph: Department of Housing and Urban Development, "Coldspring, Baltimore, Maryland", no date; 3.
    - Photograph: Department of Housing and Urban Development, "Columbia, Maryland", ca. 1967; 4.
    - Photograph: Department of Housing and Urban Development, "Columbia, Maryland", no date; 5.
    - Photograph: Department of Housing and Urban Development, "Dr John Nelson and Larry Larkins", no date; 6.
    - Photograph: Department of Housing and Urban Development, "Roosevelt Island New York City, New York", no date; 7.
  - New Community Development Corporation Board of Directors Meeting Index, 1971-1980 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    139.6
  - By-Laws, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    484.1
    - Bylaws: Community Development Corporation, no date; 1.
  - Planned Unit Development A Better Way for the Suburbs, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    105.11
  - Pre-Applications no. 39-51, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    131.6
  - The American Inst. of Architects New Communities Conference Agenda and Paper by Beckman [American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference], 1971 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    141.2
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper Presented by Biederman, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    141.3
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Carroll, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    141.4
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Crane, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    141.5
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by David, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    141.6
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Feiss, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    141.7
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Fernald, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    141.8
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Franklin, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    141.9
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Galdstone, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    141.10
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Keyes, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    141.11
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by McKellar, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    141.12
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Papers on Nasher, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    141.13
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Papers Nicoson, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    141.14
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Pillorge, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    141.15
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Rivikin, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    141.16
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Redwin, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    141.17
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Rapson, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    141.18
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Rogers, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    141.19
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Segal, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    141.20
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Tannenbaum, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    141.21
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Voorhees, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    141.22
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Warburton, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    141.23
  - American Institution of Architects New Communities Conference Paper by Watson, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    141.24
  - Index Cards to Literature on the Homeless A-Z, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    141.25
  - Index Cards to Literature on the Homeless-States and National, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    141.26
  - Pre-Applications no. 52-69 and 90, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    132.1
  - Pre-Application no. 26-38, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    131.5
  - Pre-Applications no. 1-25, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    131.4
  - Task Force on Land Use, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    80.3
  - Application Review Division Assignments, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    100.12
  - Peachtree-Summary Fact Sheets and Interviews, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    90.10
  - The Place of the Arts in New Towns, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    105.2
  - Master Index of Source Material A-D, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    93.2
  - Master Index of Source Material E-H, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    93.3
  - New Communities Cross Index, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    93.4
  - League of New Communities Material, 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    114.1
  - League of New Communities Material, 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    114.2
  - League of New Communities Material, 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    114.3
  - League of New Communities Material, 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    114.4
  - League of New Communities Material, 1973-1975 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    114.5
  - Evaluation-General, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    483.5
    - Checklist: New Communities Adminstration, "Checklist of Problems and Legislative Proposals", July 23, 1975; 1.
    - Memo: William J. Nicoson to Samuel C. Jackson, "New Legislative Proposals for New Communities", October 27, 1970; 2.
    - Report: Frederick A. McLaughlin and William J. Nicoson, "Response to Questions and Comments on New Community Legislation", February 2, 1972; 3.
  - Harbison-Declaration of Covenants, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    105.6
  - New Communities Staffing, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    96.3
  - Cross-Reference Outline Master Reference to Numbered Documents, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    138.6
  - Coordination III 3F, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    140.3
  - Watson-EO, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    138.7
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development Management III 3C, 1980s (Box 50, Folder 8)
    140.2
  - Moratorium, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    484.5
    - Press Release: Department of Housing and Urban Development, January 14, 1975; 1.
  - Equal Opportunity, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    484.3
    - Letter: J. Haines to Robinson G. Lapp, November 3, 1980; 1.
    - Memo: C. Everett Wallace to Samuel R. Pierce, Jr., "Woodlands Project - Affirmative Action Problems", November 17, 1981; 2.
    - Plan: Anonymous, "Park Central Affirmative Action Program", ca. 1979; 3.
    - Plan: Woodland Development Corporation, "The Woodlands Development Corporation Affirmative Action Plan", ca. 1982; 4.
    - Plan: Woodlands Development Corporation, "Interim Affirmative Action Plan", April 1, 1981; 5.
  - Research Institutions Around the World Concerned with Housing, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    106.5
  - Policy Information Binder, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    103.5
  - New Community Development Corporation Management Information Summary 2nd Qtr FY, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    102.6
  - New Community Development Corporation Redirection Study Working Paper, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    118.4
  - New Community Development Corporation Redirection Study Working Paper, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    118.5
  - New Community Development Corporation Board Meeting, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    98.6
  - Certificate of Eligibility, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    139.17
  - INTA (International New Towns Association), 1980 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    115.4
  - International New Town Association, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    115.5
  - INTA (International New Towns Assistant), 1981 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    116.1
  - New Community Development Corporation Program Information Summary, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    102.8
  - "The Legacy of New Communities" Revised Draft, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    139.7
  - New Community Development Corporation Program Information Summary, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    102.9
  - Cross References to Outline, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    138.9
  - Chronologies, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Titles VII New Communities Material, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    144.1
  - Titles VII New Communities Material, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    144.2
  - New Community Development Corporation Files Disposition and Description, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    139.5
  - Social Diversity, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    144.3
  - Harbison-Summary Fact Sheet, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    89.8
  - Jonathan-Summary Fact Sheets, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    89.9
  - Flower Mound-Summary Fact Sheets, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    90.1
  - Riverton-Summary Fact Sheets, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    91.3
  - Maumelle-Summary Fact Sheets, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    90.6
  - Gananda-Summary Fact Sheets, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    89.7
  - Kingwood-Summary Fact Sheets, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    90.5
  - Park Forest South-Summary Fact Sheets and Interviews, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    90.8
  - Interviews, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    82.2
  - Newfields-Summary Facts and Interviews, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    90.7
  - Weekly Report [empty]/Annual Report [empty]/ICS Interview, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    80.13
  - Staff, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    80.15
  - Title VII Summary Stats, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    139.16
  - New Community Development Corporation Management Information Summary, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    102.7
- Series 9: Publications, 1965-1983; (3 boxes)
  This series has articles, journals and press releases that were published. The series has 23 folders in 4 boxes.
  - Thomas Langman's File of Publications, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    123.2
  - Thomas Langman's File of Publications, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    123.3
  - Thomas Langman's File of Publications, 1969 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    123.4
  - Articles-New Communities-USA(New Community Surveys/Government Administration), 1969 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    104.1
  - Articles on International New Towns, 1965-1973 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    108.3
  - Articles on International New Towns, 1965-1973 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    108.4
  - Articles on International New Towns, 1965-1973 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    108.5
  - Miscellaneous Articles, 1967-1970 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    107.4
  - Miscellaneous Articles, 1967-1970 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    107.5
  - Miscellaneous Articles, 1967-1970 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    107.6
  - Journal of the American Institute of Planners, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    105.1
  - Articles-New Communities-USA (National Policy), 1970 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    104.2
  - Press Releases, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    91.6
  - Articles-New Communities-USA (Social Issues/Economic and Finance), 1972 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    104.3
  - The Washington Monthly, July/August 1973 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    106.4
  - New Community Digest, June/July 1973 and August 1974 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    105.9
  - Articles-New Communities and Urban Growth, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    94.1
  - Miscellaneous Articles, 1970-1973 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    108.1
  - Miscellaneous Articles, 1970-1973 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    108.2
  - Articles-New Communities and Urban Growth, July 1976 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    94.2
  - Articles on Land Application Systems in Environment Comment (IV-5 Innovations), 1978 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    86.5
  - Articles, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    80.14
  - Impact Journal article on New Communities Development Corporation liquidation, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    82.11
- Series 10: Books, 1969-1984; (5.5 boxes)
  This series includes workbooks, draft reviews and briefing books. The series has 42 folders in 6 boxes.
  - Greater Hartford Corporation Workbook, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    101.4
  - Columbia, Maryland: A Workshop in the Development of a New City, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    102.1
  - Columbia, Maryland: A Workshop in the Development of a New City, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    102.2
  - Nicoson Draft Handbook, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    98.1
  - Nicoson Draft Handbook, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    98.2
  - New Communities Development-Resource Book, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    111.1
  - New Communities Development-Resource Book, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    111.2
  - New Communities Development-Resource Book, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    111.3
  - Community Development Corporation Briefing Book, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    101.1
  - Community Development Corporation Briefing Book, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    101.2
  - Community Development Corporation Briefing Book, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    101.3
  - New Communities Policy Development Resource Book [copy no. 2], 1974 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    113.3
  - New Communities Policy Development Resource Book [copy no. 2], 1974 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    113.4
  - New Communities Policy Development Resource Book [copy no. 2], 1974 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    113.5
  - Community Development Corporation Briefing Book, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    112.1
  - Unlabeled folder-Underhill Book (4 Assessment of Achievements), 1980 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    83.5
  - Underhill Book-Draft Reviews Chapter II, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    83.6
  - Underhill Book Reviews Chapter II Section 4, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    83.9
  - Underhill Book Draft Reviews-Chapter II Section 6, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    84.1